[
    {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the summation of 5 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 10.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the summation of 0.21 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 5.81
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q3",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the summation of 8.1 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 2.5
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the multification of 2 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -11.2
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the multification of -2 and -5 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 10
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_3",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the subsititution of -8 and -5.6 ?(-8-(-5.6))",
        "correctAnswer": 2.5
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_3",
        "teachId": "T001",
        "question": "what is the summation of -8 and -2 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -10
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T002",
        "question": "what is the summation of 2 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 7.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T002",
        "question": "what is the summation of 0.3 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 5.9
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T002",
        "question": "what is the summation of 3 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -2.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T002",
        "question": "what is the multification of 0 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 0
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T003",
        "question": "what is the multification of -1 and -1 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 1
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T003",
        "question": "what is the multification of -5 and -5 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 25
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T003",
        "question": "what is the multification of 2 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 11.2
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T003",
        "question": "what is the multification of 2 and -5 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -10
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T004",
        "question": "what is the subsititution of -1 and -5.6 ?(-1-(-5.6))",
        "correctAnswer": 4.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T004",
        "question": "what is the subsititution of -2 and -5.6 ?(-2-(-5.6))",
        "correctAnswer": 3.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T004",
        "question": "what is the subsititution of 0 and -5.6 ?(0-(-5.6))",
        "correctAnswer": 5.6
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T004",
        "question": "what is the summation of 0 and -2 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -2
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T005",
        "question": "what is the summation of -7 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -6.4
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_1",
        "teachId": "T005",
        "question": "what is the summation of 1.21 and 5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": 6.81
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q1",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T005",
        "question": "what is the summation of 0.214 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -5.386
     },
     {
        "qId": "Q2",
        "assId": "Assignment_2",
        "teachId": "T005",
        "question": "what is the multification of 0.2 and -5.6 ?",
        "correctAnswer": -1.12
     }
]